

# **ANAND KISHORE**

# S O F T W A R E T E S T E R



+91 8248858210



https://www.linkedin.com/in/anand-kishore-9b27ba150/

documents defects, solutions and test plans accurately and clearly across diverse teams

anandkishore2528@gmail.com



8/8, Gandhi Street, Parvathi Nagar, Old Perungalathur, Chennai -600063



anandkishore2528.github.io

Resourceful Software Tester with stellar 4+ years of handling and collaborating with software developers to produce robust, bug-free programs that meet business and consumer needs. Analyzes and improves software development processes and supports teams in meeting critical project deadlines. Captures and

## EXPERIENCE

# **QA - SOFTWARE TESTER**

#### Amazon Development Center India Pvt Ltd

August 2018 - Present

- Developed and executed QA test cases, scripts and procedures for automated maintenance.
- Operated under Agile and Scrum frameworks to complete releases and well-organized sprints.
- Authored and maintained well-organized, efficient and successful manual test cases for entire team.
- Monitored resolution of bugs, tested fixes and helped developers tackle ongoing problems by providing QA perspective
- Reviewed all test cases and test scripts for quality and identified additional areas to review.
- Tested functional and compatibility of new programs or updates in comparison to existing applications.
- Assessed software bugs and compiled findings along with suggested resolutions for development team members.
- Designed, executed and maintained automated test scripts for in-project deployment.
- Created successful test scripts to manage automated feature testing.
- Completed automation of functional and regression testing.
- Kept scripts and test cases updated with current requirements.

#### QUALITY CONTROLLER

## Bradman Web Technologies Pvt Ltd

July 2017 - August 2018

- Collaborated with team to test software quality through manual and automated testing.
- Coordinated work with various teams to solve problems and improve efficiency for software testing and automation.
- Verified acceptance by developing and implementing automated and manual application features and regression tests.
- Developed, implemented and maintained automated test ware for scripts, functions and programs to boost testing efficiency.
- Operated under Agile and Scrum frameworks to complete releases and well-organized sprints.
- Carried out tests to identify, report and repair bugs and glitches.
- Built automated test scripts to handle repetitive software testing work.

# EDUCATION

## BACHELOR IN COMPUTER APPLICATION

Madras University

2021 - 2023

# DIPLOMA IN COMPUTER TECHNOLOGY

Central Polytechnic College

2024 - 2017

## SECONDARY SCHOOL LEAVING CERTIFICATE

Jai Gopal Garodia National Higher Secondary School

2013 - 2014

## EXPERTISE

#### REGRESSION. FUNCTIONAL & PERFORMANCE TESTING

## • AUTOMATION & TEST TOOLS

- Selenium/WebDriver
- TestNG
- Maven
- Jenkins

## PRODUCT MANAGEMENT

- Agile
- Scrum
- Jira

#### PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- Java
- JavaScript
- MySQL
- HTML & CSS

#### DESIGNING

- Web Designing
- Graphic Designing
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Figma

## SKILLS

#### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Working On Agile and Scrum Environments
- Analyzing Requirements Specifications Well
- Test Case Management
- Write Automation Scripts
- Bug Tracking and Resolution
- Cross Browser Compatibility
- Providing Feedback

## PERSONAL SKILLS

- Smart Working Instead of hard work
- Problem Solving
- Motivation
- Creativity
- Adaptability
- Analytical skills
- Team Work

# HOBBIES

Playing Cricket

Travelling

Learning About New Technology

Listening Music's

Freelancing